thejasminebrand.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy - theJasmineBRAND

This Privacy Policy applies only to theJasmineBrand.com (however accessed and/or used, whether via personal computers, mobile devices, or otherwise), or other interactive features that are accessible or downloadable through theJasmineBrand.com and that post a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Web Site”). This internet Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) explains how we collect, use, and safeguard information on this website. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at the web site, and does not cover any information collected at any other web site or offline by theJasmineBrand.com (unless specifically stated). By visiting theJasmineBrand.com, you acknowledge and accept the practices, terms, and conditions described in this Privacy Policy and agree that any and all disputes, including, without limitation, those disputes arising over privacy, between you and theJasmineBrand.com, employees, contributors, advertisers, sponsors, affiliates, partners, and any of their licensees, successors, and assignees, will be subject to terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and/or the Terms of Use, as applicable.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
